1649179870
When WSB is bullish, you short it. WhereÆs all the Elon D rider? Show your call position. Backup your words
When WSB is bullish, you short it. WhereÆs all the Elon D rider? Show your call position. Backup your words
1649179768
it's gone
it's gone
1649179528
I want to start doing stocks IÆm 17 some help please?
I want to start doing stocks IÆm 17 some help please?
1649179416
SST primed and ready to pop again, 0 shares to short, 0 shares returned!!
SST primed and ready to pop again, 0 shares to short, 0 shares returned!!
1649179326
Karen Musk
Karen Musk
1649179316
I can see WSB Doesn't like Heavyweights, alright then...
I can see WSB Doesn't like Heavyweights, alright then...
1649179244
The Next Millionaire Maker
The Next Millionaire Maker
1649179116
Will they let Elon buy more Twitter shares?
Will they let Elon buy more Twitter shares?
1649179077
Stocks and Futures tax software for Canada
Stocks and Futures tax software for Canada
1649179049
Dark pools
Dark pools
1649178994
Better to claim evil genius or r****d status? Wife wants to divorce and ran off to new (ex) boyfriend, I manage finances and showed her my 'smart trades' back in Sep. She now thinks I secretly hid money on the side to keep from her since there's no way you can 'lose' that much (thanks WSB stonks)
Better to claim evil genius or r****d status? Wife wants to divorce and ran off to new (ex) boyfriend, I manage finances and showed her my 'smart trades' back in Sep. She now thinks I secretly hid money on the side to keep from her since there's no way you can 'lose' that much (thanks WSB stonks)
1649178983
The Next Millionaire Maker
The Next Millionaire Maker
1649178915
Aftermathislands.io
Aftermathislands.io
1649178866
LetÆs play a gameà
LetÆs play a gameà
1649178776
Smoothbrained kid who only just recently tried messing with options - how fucked is this call?
Smoothbrained kid who only just recently tried messing with options - how fucked is this call?
1649178683
https://deepsukebe.io/?ref=xMjBC
https://deepsukebe.io/?ref=xMjBC
1649178556
LetÆs play a gameà
LetÆs play a gameà
1649178449
